The capital of the Meeres Empire
is the center of the
nation's government,
the heart of its culture,
and its financial center.
At some point, the people
began to call it...
"the most prosperous city in the world."
So this is Rayde Street.
The eunuchs were saying there's
a popular singer here.
Shall we?
I will accompany you.
I gave Zoey more work to thank her
for her help with her home village.
After you.
Thank you.
She does good work, and she pays
attention to the smallest details.
She's really grown up.
You can never have too many brilliant
people working for you, after all.
We drown in love
We long for affection and feel sorrow
Tell me, why do we meet
When we are doomed to part?
When the feckless feelings that well up
Ultimately turn into pain
Can it be blamed on an
impossible future?
I believe her name is Alichey?
I see. She isn't bad.
Her technique has room for improvement,
but I can tell she sings earnestly
and takes it seriously.
She's clearly a conscientious girl.
I try to drown my memories
of the one I love...
Why the hell are you wasting
time singing in here?!
Well?!
S-Sir, please stop!
Move!
You ain't gonna earn enough to pay
off your daddy's debt that way!
You hear?!
B-But this is all I have...
Don't make me explain the best
way for a woman to make money.
Hey.
Master...
The hell d'you want?
Go suck on your mommy's teat, kid!
Imperial Law 67, Article 2.
It is illegal to make children
assume their parents' debts.
Making her repay her father's debt,
and ordering her to sell her
body to do it, is a crime.
Don't you mess with me, you little shit!
– Ow!
– Who the hell is this kid?!
Do you wish to continue?
I'm not gonna forget this!
Hey. If those men return,
send them to me.
If you please.
A-A prince?!
That song was very nice.
How much are your living
expenses per month?
Huh? Well, um...
I also have my mother's
treatment to pay for, so...
Twenty-five rean.
Huh?
I'll pay you that much every month,
so you can concentrate on singing.
I'll increase the amount as you improve.
Thank you very much!
Now, please let me hear how it ends.
BORN BLESSED, SO I'LL
OBTAIN ULTIMATE POWER
EPISODE 2
THE BIRTH OF THE SONGSTRESS
Welcome home.
Who are they?
They called themselves lenders.
Oh, those guys?
They said they wished
to apologize to you.
Finally learned who I was, did they?
Send them away.
Tell them a prince is not someone they
can just see whenever they want.
Understood.
Well handled.
HENRY ARARAT / FOURTH PRINCE
– Brother Henry.
Granting an audience to men like
them without a second thought
would devalue the standing of
royalty and your princedom.
That is also true,
but I had another reason.
Oh?
This is not the place.
Please, come inside.
I see. You want to aid a singer?
Yes, which is why I felt that letting
them think I was still angry
would stop them from
bothering her any further.
Was her singing that good?
Please don't take her from me.
That said, I'm impressed you could
think that far ahead at your age.
Frank and Gary are closer to your
age, but they don't think that way.
Is that so?
You're all still children.
Especially Gary.
Despite all the teaching he receives,
he still hasn't learned his manners.
He will soon enough.
They may be my brothers, but
we have different mothers.
But since Henry and Gary
have the same mother,
I suppose they have a different
sort of connection.
Anyway, let's talk about
that magic sword.
It seems like you've
managed to master it.
Thanks to you, Brother.
You were right. It has its own will.
How do you carry it around, though?
Isn't it too big for you?
Actually, it isn't.
Where'd you pull that from?!
It was hidden in my sleeve.
Like this.
It taught me that itself.
This is unprecedented.
That thing was isolated as a national
treasure for two centuries,
and even the records from before
then mentioned nothing of the sort.
You are simply amazing.
My hat's off to you.
Those are the ones?
It seems so.
I can't take this anymore!
Don't you get all snotty and
ignore us, you little shit!
Don't, you idiot!
What are you doing?!
I'll kill you anytime, anyplace, damn it!
Idiot! Just keep your
head down and apologize!
What did you do this time?
I unleashed just a tiny bit of its power
and used it to threaten them.
You really have brought it to heel.
A warm welcome to you, Prince Noah.
Thank you for inviting me, Raydok.
This should be a fun evening.
That's the Thirteenth Prince?
He looks so dignified
for such a young boy.
Truly the son of His Majesty!
If I may ask, Your Highness,
what is that at your waist?
Oh, this? It's...
a gift from the Crown Prince.
It's called Leviathan.
The national treasure?!
A direct gift from the Crown Prince?!
Come to think of it, the
Thirteenth Prince's fief is Almeria...
I see! So that's the connection!
Hah! I bet it's just a toy replica.
Hold.
Were you angry because
its master was insulted?
I appreciate your loyalty,
but that was too much.
Most impressive, Your Highness!
I'm sure everyone here felt very
close to death for a moment there!
Such is the power of a national treasure!
And Your Highness has won control
over that overwhelming power!
H-He's right!
A single word from
His Highness saved our lives?
It truly is the real thing!
Most impressive,
Thirteenth Imperial Prince!
What shall we do about that man?
Leave him be.
He has nowhere left to turn anyway.
It is a pleasure to meet you,
Your Highness.
Yes.
I am Lance Rawlinson, the trader.
I cannot thank you enough for the honor
of this opportunity you have granted us.
Of course.
I am Byron Alan,
the head of the Alan Company.
I could not be more delighted
to stand in your presence.
I am his daughter, Cyndi Alan.
I see...
Is your daughter adopted, perhaps?
Y-You knew about that?
No, I can tell by looking.
Alan, you are the second or
third generation, aren't you?
Y-Yes.
Your bearing is that of one who
was born into a high rank,
but your daughter lacks that.
I see! What a keen eye you have!
What's more, you took in a
former slave as your daughter.
Y-You could deduce that?!
The moment she felt flustered,
she gave me an inquiring look.
That's a look unique to people
who have been slaves.
You are correct.
I originally bought her as a slave,
but she learns very quickly, so I've been
teaching her as my adopted daughter.
Very good. I love stories like that.
I'll invite you to my mansion sometime.
I'd like to hear more about her.
O-Of course! With pleasure!
Well, if you please.
He knows when it's time
to leave, as well.
He is a clever man.
If he stayed any longer,
he would invite too much envy.
He was the first one to be
acknowledged by the prince.
How I envy him.
There's another reason I could tell
she wasn't his real daughter.
Oh?
That's why.
She's been protecting Byron since the
first time I used the sword as a threat.
A girl her age would normally
be protected herself.
True!
How very perceptive of you
to see that from the start!
I could not be more
impressed today, Your Highness!
Well, if it isn't Noah.
OSCAR ARARAT
EIGHTH PRINCE
Brother Oscar.
What are you doing out here?
Just taking a stroll.
Without a carriage?
You always were an interesting one, Noah.
Say, if you have nothing to do,
why not join me in a treasure hunt?
I see. You meant Cobalt Street.
Oh, have you been here before?
No, I've only heard of it.
They say antiques from all over
the empire can be found here.
Plenty of counterfeits, as well.
Finding the real treasures among them is
something any noble should be able to do.
Well, no luck. We failed today.
I see.
How much is this?
Three rean.
What's this? Did you find a bargain?
No, it just made me a bit curious.
This is...
I'm sure of it!
It's the grimoire of Andrea,
the legendary sorcerer!
The original, at that!
That's a genuine treasure!
Depending on what's in it,
you could get a thousand rean for it!
Incredible! How'd you know what it was?
I didn't.
But the moment I touched it, a
plus was added to my wind stat.
I only bought it for that.
Plus?
Noah?!
Only beings with their own
will can add to my stats.
Which means this has...
What is this?!
Is this a forbidden tome with the
sorcerer's soul sealed inside?!
Run, Noah!
That's the vengeful spirit of the
great sorcerer who mastered wind!
Begone!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes... I'm fine.
Wait! Was there any damage?
No, it's fine. I aimed it upward.
He was able to make that
call in a mere instant?
When did he become that strong?
Pardon me.
Who are you?
I run an antique shop on this street.
My name is Allan Bardsley.
Having witnessed
Your Highness's remarkable feat,
I have an article that I
would like you to see.
Is it a treasure?
I do hope so.
Here it is.
It's a ring that, as I'm told,
will only show its true form
when its true owner appears.
I have shown it to many people,
but it never responds.
Isn't it just trash, then?
I thought so myself and tried
to get rid of it many times,
but it always comes back.
It comes back?
Yes. Before I know it,
it's back in my store.
So I'm quite certain
there's something to it.
That sounds interesting.
Try it on, Noah.
If you say so, Brother.
Level limit confirmed.
A voice?!
Rarity SSS.
Recognized as new owner.
Armorize.
That's... its true form?
It's armor?
There's no change in my stats.
It's not the same sort of being
as that grimoire or Leviathan,
but it seems to have many uses.
Allan, I'll take this.
I'll have payment sent to you later.
No, let me pay for this one.
Brother...
Consider it as a gift from me.
First a magic sword, then magic armor?
There really is something
different about you.
You don't want me to see you home?
No, someone is coming for me.
Thank you for today.
Die, you little shit!
Master!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
Let me go, damn it!
– Damn it!
– You again? Do you never give up?
– Settle down!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Noah, what was that?
I linked this gift from
you with Leviathan.
It seems to have reacted to his
hostility with automatic defense.
Automatic defense?
You've already mastered it? Incredible.
That lender's done for
after he attacked me.
I'll tell her that later
so she won't worry.
Hey, that was some nice singin'!
Lemme pour you a drink!
I'm sorry, but I don't...
Back off! I saw this little lady first!
Hey, that hurts! You wanna fight?!
Heh! Moron.
I-I'm sorry!
That was some amazing sword work!
You dolt! That's one of the princes!
I-I'm so sorry, Your Highness!
Are you the owner?
Don't let guys like them in here anymore.
But it's customers like them
who keep my business alive.
For the sake of my business, I...
All right, all right.
I'll purchase your business, then.
What?
Your Highness?
Zoey.
Yes, Master?
One thousand rean.
That should cover it, yes?
Y-Yes! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
U-Um, Your Highness...
I don't know how to repay you
for doing all this for me.
Just sing.
What I want from you is your music.
All you need to do is keep singing.
You like my singing that much?
Yes. I see your potential.
I want the emperor to hear you someday.
Devote yourself to singing until then.
I will!
Now, please listen to one more song.
TRANSLATION: BECKY COTTRILL
TIMING: EDGAR CRUZ
EDITING: GABRIELLA ALABANZA
QUALITY CONTROL: S BILYEU
My judgment was spot on.
This, right here,
is the real treasure.